Hey y'all, happy new year. I don't really get a big uh 2023 message for you. I'm approaching
this year like a progressive early childhood educator. I'm just gonna let it run free and
nurture whatever it discovers. As for me, I'm the same old gal. I'm still gonna say what I want on
here regardless of people telling me what I should be saying on here. I'm still not gonna fall for
that. You're fighting against black unity while expecting us to support toxicity against other
black people. I still don't think it was a good idea for you to text your ex last night who actually
put on you all of 2022 and you think could possibly be different in 2023 and you got
a little bit nostalgic and you definitely got a little bit romantic in the moment and you got
out of hand and you texted them and I know that that was a mistake and it's okay nobody's judging
you but I just want you to know that you don't have to keep the conversation going. Let the moment
have happened and let it go. This year I'm also going to continue stepping into my purpose
as an independent thinker, artist, and entrepreneur. And I hope you support that. Otherwise, let's
all just support each other in our growth and in our effort towards healing and freeing ourselves
of toxic habits that are definitely implanted in us from childhood. But I'm fine!
New Year!